(1,2,3,4)
Baby, got me looking so crazy
빠져버리는 daydream
Got me feeling you
너도 말해줄래
누가 내게 뭐라든
남들과는 달라 넌
Maybe you could be the one
날 믿어봐 한 번
I’m not looking for just fun
Maybe I could be the one
Oh baby
예민하대 나 lately
너 없이는 매일 매일이 yeah
재미없어 어쩌지
I just want you
Call my phone right now
I just wanna hear you’re mine
'Cause I know what you like boy
You’re my chemical hype boy
내 지난 날들은
눈 뜨면 잊는 꿈
Hype boy 너만 원해
Hype boy 내가 전해
And we can go high
말해봐 yeah 느껴봐 mm mm
Take him to the sky
You know I hype you boy
눈을 감아
말해봐 yeah 느껴봐 mm mm
Take him to the sky
You know I hype you boy
잠에 들려고 잠에 들려 해도
네 생각에 또 새벽 세 시 uh-oh
알려줄 거야
they can’t have you no more
봐봐 여기
내 이름 써있다고
누가 내게 뭐라든
남들과는 달라 넌
Maybe you could be the one
날 믿어봐 한 번
I’m not looking for just fun
Maybe I could be the one
Oh baby
예민하대 나 lately
너 없이는 매일 매일이 yeah
재미없어 어쩌지
I just want you
Call my phone right now
I just wanna hear you’re mine
'Cause I know what you like boy
You’re my chemical hype boy
내 지난날들은
눈 뜨면 잊는 꿈
Hype boy 너만 원해
Hype boy 내가 전해
And we can go high
말해봐 yeah
느껴봐 mm mm
Take him to the sky
You know I hype you boy
눈을 감아
말해봐 yeah
느껴봐 mm mm
Take him to the sky
You know I hype you boy